

5104 Proper Tunghaan Minglanilla, Cebu 6046 ADDRESS

(+63) 943 221 9155 PHONE

johnlloydmayol@gmail.com E-MAIL

https://github.com/mayol27

www.linkedin.com/in/johnlloyd-mayol LINKEDIN

https://mayol27.github.io ONLINE RESUME

# **ABOUT ME**

A skilled IT affluent young professional with more than 1 experience years of in Software Development & Design, Hardware and Software Maintenance and Repair, and Graphics Design enhancing PHP with in Programming Languages Codelgniter, (Laravel, Wordpress, CSS, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML, GIT, and Yarn).

# SKILLS

#### WORK

PHOTOSHOP ILLUSTRATOR LARAVEL

CODEIGNITER

PHP

# JOHN LLOYD SEGISMAR MAYOL

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

# **EXPERIENCE**

(November 2019 – Present)

#### HiPE Inc.

Software Developer

- + Wordpress
- + Laravel, SASS, CSS, HTML, GIT, and Yarn
- + Maintaining Website

(October 2019)

#### Devcash

**THESIS** 

A SOFTWARE-AS-A-SERVICE FOR CASHIERING SYSTEM FOR MICRO AND SMALL ENTERPRISES

Position: Hipster

Language: Angular.js, PHP, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML, Android, and Firebase

(October 2018 - May 2019)

#### KREDO IT ABROD INC.

**ON-THE JOB TRAINING** 

- + Hardware and Software Technical Support
- + Created Inventory System for the company

(May 2015 – October 2019)

#### **UNIVERSITY OF CEBU - MAIN CAMPUS**

**WORKING SCHOLAR** 

- + Hardware and Software Technical Support
- + Assisting students and teachers on computer laboratory
- + Sorting and filing documents

# **EDUCATION**

(June 2015 - October 2019)

University of Cebu – Main Campus

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

(June 2011 – March 2015)

Immaculate Heart of Mary Academy – Minglanilla HIGH SCHOOL

# **ORGANIZATION**

(March 2017 - Present)

GDG Cebu - Google Developers Group

(April 2015 – October 2019)

UNIVERSITY OF CEBU – ASSOCIATION OF WORKING SCHOLARS (AWS)

(June 2015 – October 2019)

UNIVERSITY OF CEBU - PHILIPPINE SOCIETY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY STUDENT (PSITS)

Wordpress

**MYSQL** 

**BOOTSTRAP** 

**CSS** 

HTML

GIT

YARN

**TROUBLESHOOT** 

**PERSONALITY** 

COMMUNICATION

**ORGANIZATION** 

TEAM PLAYER

**CREATIVITY** 

SOCIAL

# **CERTIFICATES**

(2018)

Building Entrepreneurial Ecosystem to Enhance Higher Education Value-Added for Better Graduate Employability (BEEHIVE) – MOOC

(2017)

5<sup>th</sup> UC-ICT Congress "Sharpening Junior Mobile Technologists"

(2016)

4<sup>th</sup> UC-ICT Congress "Shaping up Creative Minds through Great UX Design"

# **REFERENCE**

# Ms. Ma. Catherine Carumba

Secretary – College of Computer Studies

Contact: 255 – 7777 loc. 113

Ms. Lina J. Perez

UCEMPC – Secretary Contact: 255 – 7777 loc. 136

Ms. Jerrah Marie Son

Laboratory Supervisor – CCS

Contact: 0923 - 866 - 7880